That in China,
do it, do it
[Music]
Hello friends, welcome to the
wonderful video of Apraad Market Thanda YouTube channel
and friends, today we are going to talk
about insurance companies.
So friends, in the share market, these three
companies which I have put on your screen, these are insurance companies
and if you want, you can
answer these questions for life time,
it is up to you, it can be your sale
decision, you should do a
little about these companies and after studying them,
you should take a decision. So
friends, today we are going to talk
about this company, its name is
ICICI.
This company is registered under the name ICICI Prudential
and its share reservation in the share market
is two, you can see it at 64 thousand 637 crores,
so friends,
a great news related to this company has
come in the market and regarding this,
we can get to see a good episode of Bigg Boss in the future.
Friends, when we talk about this news,
what is Bigg Boss, then friends
Look at this, ICICI Lombard, which is
Bharti AXA Life Insurance, is a company that is
not even listed on the stock market,
and the company that is acquiring this company is
ICICI Lombard, which is a company
in the stock market, and is going to
transact this company for Rs 26 crores.
Friends, it is going to wrap up the general insurance company for Rs 26 crores,
meaning it is going to
add it to its portfolio
and is going to establish its dominance
in the insurance sector of the stock market. So,
this company is Indian Porn Channel Life
Insurance Company. Almost everyone knows this company. It is
counted among the top most companies of India. It
comes later and is considered a very good insurance company.
Friends, this company is
also going to be
bought by ICICI Bank for Rs 26 crores. Friends, the
secret is that there can be a guarantee of being a man in it,
and this merger will be possible only
after permission from the government,
but the talks about it have started circulating in the market.
Friends,
look at its profit regarding this company, the first
quarter's profit was Raghu 59 crores and the
financial year was less than any financial year.  In the first quarter of the year, there has been a
12% decline in it,
so friends, there are talks that this company is going to merge with
ICICI Lombard
and let's see
what happens next about this company, so
friends, this appointment
was related to the general insurance company Meena and how did you like the video,
please tell me by commenting and
if you have not subscribed to this channel yet, then
subscribe quickly and
press the bell icon, let's meet
in the next video, till then go to
[Music]
Ajay